Hello.
こんにちは
That's good.
いい ですね
You're young.
若いね
What do you usually do?
普段何やってる人ですか?
I go to a beauty school.
美容の専門学校通ってます
Like this
こんな
Can I come over?
ところ 来ちゃっていいですか?
Don't have enough money?
お金が足りないですか?
I receive some allowance, but it's not much.
仕送りもらってるんですけど、やっぱ少ないんで
I agree.
そうですね
It's no good living today.
今日で暮らすのダメですね
That's right.
そうなんですよ
I'm not there right now.
今いないです
Don't you have a part-time job?
バイトとかしてないの?
My part-time job is at a pub,
バイトは居酒屋でバイトしてるんですけど、
It's not like the hourly wage is that good.
そんなめっちゃ時給いいわけでもないんで
Don't you do Fusun?
フーズンはやらないんですか?
I haven't.
してないです
Why not?
しないですか?
Are you scared?
怖 いですか?
The classes are quite difficult.
授業が結構大変です
Like Coupile?
クーピーレとか?
that's right.
そう です
Show me this
これ 見せて
please.
ください
Where is it?
ど こだろう?
difficult.
難しい
Raw liver?
生肝体か
difficult.
難しい
But I prefer kind eyes.
でも優しい目の方が好きです
It's difficult.
難しいんですよ
Is it true?
本当ですか?
What is your score out of 100?
100点満点、何点ですか?
It's difficult.
むずい
About 70 to 80.
70から80くらい
amazing.
すごい
Isn't that a super passing score?
超合格点じゃないですか?
Is it true?
本当ですか?
That means she's a naughty girl.
ヘッチな子ってことですね
After all, you can go to most schools.
だって、大体の学試合校行けちゃいますよ
surely.
確かに
study
学
This is not the time to go to school.
校 行っている場合じゃないですよ
As expected of beauty.
さすが美容
That's right.
そうですよね
This is already an izakaya.
これはもう居酒屋ありなんですね
I agree.
そうですね
Izakaya is quite popular.
居酒屋は割と
If you have a hard time getting a job, you won't go.
なかなか就職しちゃうと行かないんですからね
amazing.
すごい
It's not smooth.
つるつるじゃないですと
As I went to school for normal beauty,
普通の美容を学校行っているだけあって、
Are you careful?
気を使ってますか?
a little bit.
ちょっと
Do you have any dreams for the future?
将来の夢はありますか?
Hairdresser.
美容師さん
That's right.
そうなんですね
Like independence.
独立みたいな
I agree.
そうですね
Number one.
一番は
I don't have a cold.
風邪はないですね
Just a little bit, yeah.
そのままちょっと、そう
I understand.
分かってますね
I can see it.
見えそう
I can't see it.
見えない
Lucky cable.
ラッキースケーブル
Scrable.
スケーブル
It's something like this
こういう風なものです
But.
けど
Down, down.
下、 下
I'm taking pictures.
撮ってる
Ah, beautiful.
あ〜、美しい
It seems possible.
できそう
Are you happy?
嬉しいの?
like?
好き?
I can go.
いけるぞ
You're really moving on your own, aren't you?
めっちゃ自分で動いてるでしょ
Ah, I think I can go.
あ〜、いけそう
Ah, I'm so happy.
あ〜、嬉しい
Ah, amazing.
あ〜、すごい
Slowly, it feels good.
ゆ っ く り、気持ちいい
Ah, amazing.
あ〜、すごい
Slow down, it feels good.
ゆっくり、気持ちいい
amazing.
すごい
Ah, I think I can go.
あ〜、いけそう